# LORENZ TUBO



**6**47-394-5802

✓ lorenzalvintubo@gmail.com

22 Olive Avenue, North York

https://lorenzalvintuboresume.netlify.app/

https://github.com/YuhanPizza

## PROFILE

Currently a Computer programming student at Seneca college. Trying to learn all to broaden my knowledge on the subject. Have done a few side projects with different programming languages. Although I have no programming job experience I have a lot of work experience and I think this qualifies my to work on a team environment.

## SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Analytical and Logical Thinking
- Front End and Back End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

# PREVIOUS WORK EXPERIENCE

SHIPPING SUPERVISOR

Nella Cutlery

August 2021-March 2022

- Managed a team of expert knife smiths to create top of the line hand crafted Knives.
- Managed Delivery schedules on a weekly basis reducing loss and returns to make on time deliveries.
- Planned and talked with the drivers to plan their routes daily.

#### **BAKER**

Sweets from the Earth

October 2020 - July 2021

- Able to Bake a variety of different pastries accordingly.
- Altered ingredients and processes to improve the products taste.
- Well accustomed to team environments that required strong communication.

### BAKER

FGF foods March 2019 - Feb 2020

- Honed my craft at creating more diverse recipes for a wide array of pastry products.
- Handled a large team of people for a large pastry supply company able to create 500,000 products overnight.

## EDUCATION

# BACHELORS DEGREE IN COMMUNICATION

Holy Name University 2012-2016

# DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER PROGRAMING(EXPECTED)

Seneca College 2022-2023(expected) Honor's List for Summer2022 Honor's List for Fall 2022